Guide to the Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 2
Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 2
- Box: 5, Folder: 47, Publication (Box 5, Folder 47)
  - Item 1: People Come First, Publication (Box 5, Folder 47)
    Author: William F. Gutwein
  - Item 2: Group Insurance and Pension Plans for Employees and Their Dependents, Publication (Box 5, Folder 47)
    Author: C.T. Dearing Printing Company
- Box: 5, Folder: 48, Publication (Box 5, Folder 48)
  - Item 1: Your Ideas Can Be Worth Cash, 1949; Publication (Box 5, Folder 48)
    Author: Cudaly Packing Company
- Box: 5, Folder: 49, Publication (Box 5, Folder 49)
  - Item 1: Creative Artists Public Service Program, Publication (Box 5, Folder 49)
    Author: Cultural Council Foundation
- Box: 5, Folder: 50, Publication (Box 5, Folder 50)
  - Item 1: Rules and Regulations of the Benefit Department, Publication (Box 5, Folder 50)
    Author: Curtis Lumber and Millwork Co.
- Box: 5, Folder: 51, Publication (Box 5, Folder 51)
  - Item 1: The New Look in Metallurgy, 1966; Publication (Box 5, Folder 51)
    Author: Curtiss-Wright Corp.
  - Item 2: Agreement, 1959; Publication (Box 5, Folder 51)
    Notes: Sept. 18
- Box: 5, Folder: 52, Publication (Box 5, Folder 52)
  - Item 1: Your Retirement Plan, 1948; Publication (Box 5, Folder 52)
    Author: Cutter Laboratories
- Box: 5, Folder: 53, Publication (Box 5, Folder 53)
  - Item 1: "Let's Talk Shop", Publication (Box 5, Folder 53)
    Author: Cutler Hammer, Inc.
  - Item 2: The Company and You, 1959; Publication (Box 5, Folder 53)
- Box: 5, Folder: 54, Publication (Box 5, Folder 54)
  - Item 1: Successful Dairy Farmer I Have to be a Practical Man, Publication (Box 5, Folder 54)
    Author: Dairymen's League
  - Item 2: A Milk Markeeting Organization Owned and Operated by and for Farmers, Publication (Box 5, Folder 54)
  - Item 3: Dairymen's League News, 1956; Publication (Box 5, Folder 54)
    Notes: Vol. 40, No. 18 Aug. 28
- Box: 6, Folder: 1, Publication (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Annual Report, 1968; Publication (Box 6, Folder 1)
    Author: Dan River Mills, Inc.
  - Item 2: Focus, 1969; Publication (Box 6, Folder 1)
    Notes: Vol. 5, No. 2 March-April
  - Item 3: Suggestion Plan, Publication (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Item 4: Annual Report, 1967; Publication (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Item 5: The Dan River Story, Publication (Box 6, Folder 1)
- Box: 6, Folder: 2, Publication (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: The Wrinkle is Dead, Publication (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Item 2: A Dictionary of Textile Terms, 1967; Publication (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Item 3: All About "Preset" Dan-Press, Publication (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Item 4: First in American Fabrics, Publication (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Item 5: A Brief History of Dan River, Publication (Box 6, Folder 2)
- Box: 6, Folder: 3, Publication (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: The Dan River Pattern, Publication (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Item 2: Employee Handbook, 1968; Publication (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Item 3: Opportunity at Dan River Mills for the College Man, Publication (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Item 4: Information Sheet and conditions for Manuscript Use, 1975; Publication (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Item 5: Supervisor's Manual, 1955; Publication (Box 6, Folder 3)
    Notes: 3/28
- Box: 6, Folder: 4, Publication (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Safety Suggestions, Publication (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Item 2: Your Dan River Pension Plan, 1953; Publication (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Item 3: Group Medical Surgical Plan, Publication (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Item 4: Group Life Insurance Plan, Publication (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Item 5: Position Description: Clerical, Technical, and Supervisory Evaluaiton Plan, 1952; Publication (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Item 6: The Evaluation Plan and its Use, 1952; Publication (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Item 7: Summary of the Evaluation Plan for Clerical, Technical and Supervisory Positions, Publication (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Item 8: The Evaluation Plan and its Use, 1952; Publication (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Item 9: The Dan River Mills Profit Sharing Plan, Publication (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Item 10: Supervisory Training Program, 1968; Publication (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Item 11: Dean River Evening School Training Program, Publication (Box 6, Folder 4)
- Box: 6, Folder: 5, Publication (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Personal December Planning Calendar, 1971; Publication (Box 6, Folder 5)
    Author: Dartnell
  - Item 2: 1972 Chart for Scheduling Vacations and Charting Absenteeism, Publication (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Item 3: Building an Effective and Acceptable Corporate Image, Publication (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Item 4: It's an Idea, Publication (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Item 5: How Kemper Insurance Office Produces Better Bulletin Boards, Publication (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Item 6: Here's an Idea!, Publication (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Item 7: An Error Becomes a Blunder When it's Repeated, Publication (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Item 8: Communications, Publication (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Item 9: Carelessness Can Foul Things Up, Publication (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Item 10: Help Flatten Waste, Publication (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Item 11: You Can Lose More Than an Argument!, Publication (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Item 12: The Three Blind Mice: Cut Off Their Tails With a Cost-Cutting Knife, Publication (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Item 13: Clerical Incentives: A Key to Reducing Office Costs, Publication (Box 6, Folder 5)
    Author: R.J. Little: W.L. Davidson
  - Item 14: Dartnell Survey of Sales Training Practices, Publication (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Item 15: Should You or Shouldn't You Engage a Consultant?, Publication (Box 6, Folder 5)
    Author: Richard J. Steele
  - Item 16: Successful Management Methods, Publication (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Item 17: What an Executive Should Know About Managing His Own Finances, Publication (Box 6, Folder 5)
    Author: Richard Frisbie
  - Item 18: Year at a Glance Executive Planner, 1972; Publication (Box 6, Folder 5)
- Box: 6, Folder: 6, Publication (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Techniques for Spotting and Developing Employees Likely to Make Good Supervisory or Executive Material in Your Company, Publication (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Item 2: How to Select Better Salesmen, Executives, Office and S Employeesupervisory, Publication (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Item 3: Dartnell's New Personnel Administration Service, Publication (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Item 4: Personnel Adminstration: How the NLRB Applies New Jurisdictional Standards, Publication (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Item 5: Executive and Supervisory Development, 1953; Publication (Box 6, Folder 6)
    Author: Robert N. McMurry
  - Item 6: Methods Research in Management, Publication (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Item 7: Writing Letters to Employees' Homes, Publication (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Item 8: How Midland Cooperatives Administers its Salary Program in Executive and Supervisory Salary Levels, Publication (Box 6, Folder 6)
- Box: 6, Folder: 7, Publication (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Constitution and By-Laws, 1956; Publication (Box 6, Folder 7)
    Author: David Smith Steel Company
- Box: 6, Folder: 8, Publication (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Your Life at davidson, Publication (Box 6, Folder 8)
    Author: Davidson Publishing Company
  - Item 2: Welcome to DPC, Publication (Box 6, Folder 8)
- Box: 6, Folder: 9, Publication (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: What it Means to be a Supervisor at Daystrom, Publication (Box 6, Folder 9)
    Author: Daystrom, Inc.
  - Item 2: National Defense Program Manpower Policies of Daystrom, Inc., Publication (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Item 3: Your Insurance, 1953; Publication (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Item 4: Employee Accident and Sickness Benefits, 1959; Publication (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Item 5: Your Incentive Play Plan, Publication (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Item 6: Why Job Evaluation?, Publication (Box 6, Folder 9)
- Box: 6, Folder: 10, Publication (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: Agreement, 1952; Publication (Box 6, Folder 10)
    Notes: Feb. 29 3 copies
  - Item 2: Agreement, 1958; Publication (Box 6, Folder 10)
    Notes: March 12
  - Item 3: Agreement, 1948; Publication (Box 6, Folder 10)
    Notes: April 19
  - Item 4: By-Laws and Constitution, 1959; Publication (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Item 5: To All Hourly Employees, 1954; Publication (Box 6, Folder 10)
    Notes: Feb. 20 1954
  - Item 6: Dear Fellow Employees, 1953; Publication (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Item 7: To Our Friends in the Community, 1954; Publication (Box 6, Folder 10)
    Notes: Feb. 11
  - Item 8: Jan. 18, 1954; Publication (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Item 9: Letter, 1959; Publication (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Item 10: Arbitration Award, 1958; Publication (Box 6, Folder 10)
    Notes: Jan. 8
  - Item 11: Organization Chart, Publication (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Item 12: Strike Over, Two Plants Re-Open, 1954; Publication (Box 6, Folder 10)
    Notes: March 8
  - Item 13: Union Calls at Daystrom Pickets, 1954; Publication (Box 6, Folder 10)
    Notes: March 4
  - Item 14: Daystrom to Leave March 1955, Childs Says; 700 Idled by Strike, 1954; Publication (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Item 15: Daystrom Strike Brings Company Threat to move, 1954; Publication (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Item 16: Daystrom Strike Ends; Workers Return to Plant, 1954; Publication (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Item 17: Union Workers Daystrom Plant Return to Jobs, 1954; Publication (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Item 18: Daystrom Plant Strike is Ended, 1954; Publication (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Item 19: Strike at Daystrom's Idles 100 More; Office Layoff Starts, 1954; Publication (Box 6, Folder 10)
    Notes: March 3
- Box: 6, Folder: 11, Publication (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: Daystrom Flash, 1952; Publication (Box 6, Folder 11)
    Notes: July 25
  - Item 2: Daystrom Flash, 1953; Publication (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Item 3: Suggestion and Award System, 1958; Publication (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Item 4: Dear Fellow Employees, 1953; Publication (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Item 5: Furniture News, 1958; Publication (Box 6, Folder 11)
    Notes: Vol. 1, No. 7 Dec.
  - Item 6: 59th Annual Report to our Stockholders, 1952; Publication (Box 6, Folder 11)
- Box: 6, Folder: 12, Publication (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: Here's to Your Health, Publication (Box 6, Folder 12)
    Author: Dayton Company
- Box: 6, Folder: 13, Publication (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: Dayton Power and Light Company, 1959; Publication (Box 6, Folder 13)
    Author: Dayton Power and Light Company
- Box: 6, Folder: 14, Publication (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Item 1: JD Journal, 1977; Publication (Box 6, Folder 14)
    Author: Deere and Company
    Notes: Vol. 6, No. 2 Summer
  - Item 2: The Furrow, 1977; Publication (Box 6, Folder 14)
    Notes: July/Aug.
  - Item 3: The Furrow, 1977; Publication (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Item 4: The Furrow, 1977; Publication (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Item 5: JD Journal, 1977; Publication (Box 6, Folder 14)
    Notes: Vol. 6, No. 1 Spring
- Box: 6, Folder: 15, Publication (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Item 1: Your Calpak Retirement Plan, 1958; Publication (Box 6, Folder 15)
    Author: Del Monte Food Products Co.
- Box: 6, Folder: 16, Publication (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Item 1: Your Job at Delavans, Publication (Box 6, Folder 16)
    Author: Delavans
- Box: 6, Folder: 17, Publication (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Item 1: To Conductors Saratoga & Champlain Divisions, 1985; Publication (Box 6, Folder 17)
    Author: Delaware and Hudson Canal Co.
    Notes: Several copies Dec. 7
- Box: 6, Folder: 18, Publication (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Item 1: Retirement Plan, 1953; Publication (Box 6, Folder 18)
    Author: Delaware Power and Light Co.
- Box: 6, Folder: 19, Publication (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Item 1: Merry Christmas, 1953; Publication (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Item 2: Annual Report, 1952; Publication (Box 6, Folder 19)
- Box: 6, Folder: 20, Publication (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Item 1: A Handbook for Non Bargaining Unit Employees of the University of Delaware, Publication (Box 6, Folder 20)
    Author: Delaware University
- Box: 6, Folder: 21, Publication (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - Item 1: Licking the Employee Contribution Problem with a "Buck-a-Month" Club, Publication (Box 6, Folder 21)
    Author: Delta Air Lines
- Box: 6, Folder: 22, Publication (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - Item 1: The Librarian, 1962; Publication (Box 6, Folder 22)
    Author: Demco Library Supplies
- Box: 6, Folder: 23, Publication (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - Item 1: The Suggestion System, Publication (Box 6, Folder 23)
    Author: Dennison Manufacturing Company
  - Item 2: Dennison News, 1952; Publication (Box 6, Folder 23)
    Notes: Vol. 2, No. 2 March
  - Item 3: 1951 Annual Report 107th Year, Publication (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - Item 4: Dennison News, 1960; Publication (Box 6, Folder 23)
    Notes: Vol. 10, No. 2 March
  - Item 5: Your Dennison Guide, 1956; Publication (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - Item 6: General Information for Foremen, Publication (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - Item 7: Rules and Regulations Covering Vacations with Pay for hourly Employees, 1952; Publication (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - Item 8: Employment Application, Publication (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - Item 9: Separation Allowance Plan, 1949; Publication (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - Item 10: Accident and Sickness Benefit Plan, 1949; Publication (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - Item 11: Summary of Retirement Plan for Employees of Denison Manufacturing Company, 1954; Publication (Box 6, Folder 23)
- Box: 6, Folder: 24, Publication (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - Item 1: A Handbook for Correspondence: The Poster, Publication (Box 6, Folder 24)
    Author: Denver Post
- Box: 6, Folder: 25, Publication (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - Item 1: Working With the University of Denver, Publication (Box 6, Folder 25)
    Author: Denver University
- Box: 6, Folder: 26, Publication (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - Item 1: Communications Manual, 1962; Publication (Box 6, Folder 26)
    Author: Constance M. Wagner
  - Item 2: Communications Manual, 1954; Publication (Box 6, Folder 26)
- Box: 6, Folder: 27, Publication (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - Item 1: Department of Street Railways Resolution, 1953; Publication (Box 6, Folder 27)
    Author: City of Detroit
  - Item 2: Manual of Standard Personnel Practices for the City of Detroit, 1955; Publication (Box 6, Folder 27)
    Author: The Civil Service Commission
- Box: 6, Folder: 28, Publication (Box 6, Folder 28)
  - Item 1: The DSR Reporter, 1953; Publication (Box 6, Folder 28)
    Author: Detroit Department of Street Railways
  - Item 2: Annual Report, 1953; Publication (Box 6, Folder 28)
  - Item 3: Rules and Regulations Governing Conditions of Employment for Transportation Equipment Operations, 1954; Publication (Box 6, Folder 28)
- Box: 6, Folder: 29, Publication (Box 6, Folder 29)
  - Item 1: Synchroscope, 1967; Publication (Box 6, Folder 29)
    Author: Detroit Edison Co.
  - Item 2: Synchroscope, 1967; Publication (Box 6, Folder 29)
  - Item 3: Coal to Kilowatts, 1956; Publication (Box 6, Folder 29)
  - Item 4: Power Plant Study, 1954; Publication (Box 6, Folder 29)
    Author: Survey Research Center
  - Item 5: Absences and Employee Attitudes in an Electric Power Company, 1952; Publication (Box 6, Folder 29)
    Author: Flord Mann and Howard Baumgartel
  - Item 6: Annual Report, 1962; Publication (Box 6, Folder 29)
  - Item 7: Annual Report, 1958; Publication (Box 6, Folder 29)
  - Item 8: Annual Report, 1955; Publication (Box 6, Folder 29)
  - Item 9: Annual Report, 1952; Publication (Box 6, Folder 29)
  - Item 10: Partners in Progress, 1953; Publication (Box 6, Folder 29)
- Box: 6, Folder: 30, Publication (Box 6, Folder 30)
  - Item 1: Edison Management News, 1972; Publication (Box 6, Folder 30)
    Notes: May 23
  - Item 2: Edison Management News, 1972; Publication (Box 6, Folder 30)
    Notes: Aug. 10, 1972
  - Item 3: Edison Management News, 1972; Publication (Box 6, Folder 30)
    Notes: Aug. 21
  - Item 4: Edison Management News, 1972; Publication (Box 6, Folder 30)
  - Item 5: Edison Management News, 1972; Publication (Box 6, Folder 30)
    Notes: June 21
  - Item 6: Edison Management News, 1972; Publication (Box 6, Folder 30)
    Notes: June 20
  - Item 7: Edison Management News, 1972; Publication (Box 6, Folder 30)
    Notes: July 28
  - Item 8: Edison Management News, 1972; Publication (Box 6, Folder 30)
  - Item 9: Edison Management News, 1972; Publication (Box 6, Folder 30)
  - Item 10: Edison Management News, 1972; Publication (Box 6, Folder 30)
    Notes: Sept. 19
  - Item 11: Edison Management News, 1972; Publication (Box 6, Folder 30)
    Notes: Sept. 5, 1972
  - Item 12: Edison Management News, 1972; Publication (Box 6, Folder 30)
    Notes: Aug. 23
  - Item 13: Edison Management News, 1972; Publication (Box 6, Folder 30)
    Author: Sept. 19
    Notes: July 12
  - Item 14: Edison Management News, 1972; Publication (Box 6, Folder 30)
    Notes: July 5
  - Item 15: Edison Management News, 1972; Publication (Box 6, Folder 30)
    Notes: Oct. 31
  - Item 16: Edison Management News, 1972; Publication (Box 6, Folder 30)
    Notes: Oct. 19
  - Item 17: Edison Management News, 1973; Publication (Box 6, Folder 30)
    Notes: Feb. 13
  - Item 18: Edison Management News, 1973; Publication (Box 6, Folder 30)
    Notes: Feb. 5
  - Item 19: Edison Management News, 1973; Publication (Box 6, Folder 30)
    Notes: Feb. 2
  - Item 20: Edison Management News, 1972; Publication (Box 6, Folder 30)
    Notes: Dec. 11
  - Item 21: Edison Management News, 1973; Publication (Box 6, Folder 30)
    Notes: Jan. 26
  - Item 22: Edison Management News, 1972; Publication (Box 6, Folder 30)
    Notes: Nov. 10
  - Item 23: Edison Management News, 1972; Publication (Box 6, Folder 30)
    Notes: Nov. 8
  - Item 24: Edison Management News, 1972; Publication (Box 6, Folder 30)
    Notes: Nov. 15
  - Item 25: Edison Management News, 1972; Publication (Box 6, Folder 30)
    Notes: Dec. 1
  - Item 26: Edison Management News, 1972; Publication (Box 6, Folder 30)
    Notes: Nov. 29
  - Item 27: Edison Management News, 1973; Publication (Box 6, Folder 30)
    Notes: Feb. 21
  - Item 28: Edison Management News, 1973; Publication (Box 6, Folder 30)
    Notes: Feb. 23
  - Item 29: Edison Management News, 1973; Publication (Box 6, Folder 30)
    Notes: March 2
  - Item 30: Edison Management News, 1973; Publication (Box 6, Folder 30)
    Notes: March 21
  - Item 31: Edison Management News, 1973; Publication (Box 6, Folder 30)
  - Item 32: News Briefs, 1971; Publication (Box 6, Folder 30)
    Notes: Vol. 4, No. 42 Oct. 21
  - Item 33: News Briefs, 1971; Publication (Box 6, Folder 30)
    Notes: Vol. 4, No. 38 Sept. 23
  - Item 34: News Briefs, 1971; Publication (Box 6, Folder 30)
    Notes: Vol. 4, No. 34 Aug. 26
  - Item 35: News Briefs, 1971; Publication (Box 6, Folder 30)
    Notes: Vol. 4, No. 36 Sept. 9
  - Item 36: News Briefs, 1971; Publication (Box 6, Folder 30)
    Notes: Vol. 4, No. 37 Sept. 16
  - Item 37: News Briefs, 1971; Publication (Box 6, Folder 30)
    Notes: Vol. 4, No. 32 Aug. 12
  - Item 38: News Briefs, 1971; Publication (Box 6, Folder 30)
    Notes: Vol. 4, No. 43 Oct. 28
  - Item 39: News Briefs, 1971; Publication (Box 6, Folder 30)
    Notes: Vol. 4, No. 41 Oct. 14
  - Item 40: News Briefs, 1971; Publication (Box 6, Folder 30)
    Notes: Vol. 4, No. 39 Sept. 30
  - Item 41: News Briefs, 1971; Publication (Box 6, Folder 30)
    Notes: Vol. 4, No. 40 Oct. 7
  - Item 42: News Briefs, 1971; Publication (Box 6, Folder 30)
    Notes: Vol. 4, No. 30 July 29
  - Item 43: News Briefs, 1971; Publication (Box 6, Folder 30)
    Notes: Vol. 4, No. 31 Aug. 5
  - Item 44: News Briefs, 1971; Publication (Box 6, Folder 30)
    Notes: Vol. 4, No. 28 July 15
  - Item 45: News Briefs, 1971; Publication (Box 6, Folder 30)
    Notes: Vol. 4, No. 29 July 22
  - Item 46: News Briefs, 1971; Publication (Box 6, Folder 30)
    Notes: Vol. 4, No. 23 June 10
  - Item 47: News Briefs, 1971; Publication (Box 6, Folder 30)
    Notes: Vol. 4, No. 24 June 17
  - Item 48: News Briefs, 1971; Publication (Box 6, Folder 30)
    Notes: Vol. 4, No. 27 July 8
  - Item 49: News Briefs, 1971; Publication (Box 6, Folder 30)
    Notes: Vol. 4, no. 22 June 3
  - Item 50: News Briefs, 1971; Publication (Box 6, Folder 30)
    Notes: Vol. 4, No.21 May 27
  - Item 51: News Briefs, 1971; Publication (Box 6, Folder 30)
    Notes: Vol. 4, No. 26 July 1
  - Item 52: News Briefs, 1971; Publication (Box 6, Folder 30)
    Notes: Vol. 4, No. 9 March 3
  - Item 53: News Briefs, 1971; Publication (Box 6, Folder 30)
    Notes: Vol. 4, No. 12 March 24
  - Item 54: News Briefs, 1971; Publication (Box 6, Folder 30)
    Notes: Vol. 4, No. 13 March 31
  - Item 55: News Briefs, 1971; Publication (Box 6, Folder 30)
    Notes: Vol. 4, No. 11 March 17
  - Item 56: News Briefs, 1971; Publication (Box 6, Folder 30)
    Notes: Vol. 4, No. 13 April 15
  - Item 57: News Briefs, 1971; Publication (Box 6, Folder 30)
    Notes: Vol. 4, No. 16 April 22
  - Item 58: News Briefs, 1971; Publication (Box 6, Folder 30)
    Notes: Vol. 4, No. 17 April 29
  - Item 59: News Briefs, 1971; Publication (Box 6, Folder 30)
    Notes: Vol. 4, No. 18 May 6
  - Item 60: News Briefs, 1971; Publication (Box 6, Folder 30)
  - Item 61: New Briefs, 1971; Publication (Box 6, Folder 30)
    Notes: Vol. 4, No.7 Feb. 18
  - Item 62: News Briefs, 1971; Publication (Box 6, Folder 30)
    Notes: Vol. 4, No. 5 Feb. 3
  - Item 63: News Briefs, 1971; Publication (Box 6, Folder 30)
    Notes: Vol. 4, No. 10 March 10
  - Item 64: News Briefs, 1971; Publication (Box 6, Folder 30)
    Notes: Vol. 4, No. 20 May 20
  - Item 65: News Briefs, 1971; Publication (Box 6, Folder 30)
    Notes: Vol. 4, No. 19 May 13
  - Item 66: News Briefs, 1971; Publication (Box 6, Folder 30)
    Notes: Vol. 4, No. 8 Feb. 24
  - Item 67: News Briefs, 1971; Publication (Box 6, Folder 30)
    Notes: Vol. 4, No. 6 Feb. 10
  - Item 68: News Briefs, 1971; Publication (Box 6, Folder 30)
  - Item 69: News Briefs, 1970; Publication (Box 6, Folder 30)
    Notes: Vol. 3, No. 37 Sept. 10
  - Item 70: News Briefs, 1970; Publication (Box 6, Folder 30)
    Notes: Vol. 3, No. 27 July 1
  - Item 71: News Briefs, 1970; Publication (Box 6, Folder 30)
    Notes: Vol. 3, No. 29 July 15
  - Item 72: News Briefs, 1970; Publication (Box 6, Folder 30)
    Notes: Vol. 3, No. 30 July 22
  - 1970, Publication (Box 6, Folder 30)
  - Item 74: News Briefs, 1970; Publication (Box 6, Folder 30)
    Notes: Vol. 3, No. 31 July 29
  - Item 75: News Briefs, 1970; Publication (Box 6, Folder 30)
    Notes: Vol. 3, No. 28 July 8
  - Item 76: News Briefs, 1970; Publication (Box 6, Folder 30)
    Notes: Vol. 3, No. 33 Aug. 12
  - Item 77: News Briefs, 1970; Publication (Box 6, Folder 30)
    Notes: Vol. 3, No. 24 June 10
  - Item 78: News Briefs, 1970; Publication (Box 6, Folder 30)
    Notes: Vol. 3, No. 26 June 24
  - Item 79: News Briefs, 1970; Publication (Box 6, Folder 30)
    Notes: Vol. 3, No. 25 June 17
  - Item 80: News Briefs, 1970; Publication (Box 6, Folder 30)
    Notes: Vol. 3, No. 35 Aug. 26
  - Item 81: News Briefs, 1970; Publication (Box 6, Folder 30)
    Notes: Vol. 3, No. 34 Aug. 19
  - Item 82: News Briefs, 1969; Publication (Box 6, Folder 30)
    Notes: Vol. 2, No. 37 Sept. 10
  - Item 83: News Briefs, 1969; Publication (Box 6, Folder 30)
    Notes: Vol. 2, No. 42 Oct. 15
  - Item 84: News Briefs, 1969; Publication (Box 6, Folder 30)
    Notes: Vol. 2, No. 43 Oct. 22
  - Item 85: News Briefs, 1969; Publication (Box 6, Folder 30)
    Notes: Vol. 2, No. 31 July 30
  - Item 86: News Briefs, 1969; Publication (Box 6, Folder 30)
    Notes: Vol. 2, No. 36 Sept. 4
  - Item 87: News Briefs, 1969; Publication (Box 6, Folder 30)
    Notes: Vol. 2, No. 39 Sept. 24
  - Item 88: News Briefs, 1969; Publication (Box 6, Folder 30)
    Notes: Vol. 2, No. 38 Sept. 17
  - Item 89: News Briefs, 1969; Publication (Box 6, Folder 30)
    Notes: Vol. 2, No. 40 Oct. 1
  - Item 90: News Briefs, 1969; Publication (Box 6, Folder 30)
    Notes: Vol. 2, No. 41 Oct. 8
  - Item 91: News Briefs, 1969; Publication (Box 6, Folder 30)